

# **Rudy Chen**

rudy871211@gmail.com

**y** @OoAaazz

M

https://medium.com/ @OoAAAZZZoO

#### INTRODUCTION

I have joined crypto world since 2021 Jun. After that, I realized the power of the blockchain will change the world and decided to invest not only my money but also my time, my energy here.

I'm an outgoing person and like to take adventure. To me, crypto world is in wild west era. I'm really happy to work in this industry because I can find new things every hours.

#### **SKILLS**

#### **English**

lelts: 7.5 Listen : 8.5 Reading : 9 Speaking : 6.5 Writing : 6

Python/React/Js/html/css

Smart Contract (solidity)

Dune analytics (MySQL)

# WORK EXPERIENCE (CRYPTO ONLY)

#### **BNBPAY**

# Community & Operation

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

- Connecting to KOLs
- Managing telegram community
- Traslating the white paper from English to Chinese

### **TOKEN INSIGHT**

### **Analyst**

Dec 2021 - May 2022

- Writing articles about the market hot spot
- Maintaining the crypto database
- Discovering new projects and doing research

### **EQUOLL FINANCE (ON BNB CHAIN)**

# **Operation**

May 2022 - present

Sep 2017 - Jan 2022

- Writing protocol documentation
- Organizing the community events

### **DOPEX (OPTION ON ARBITRUM)**

### Contributor

• Community events, articles, etc.

#### MEANWHILE....

I spend rest of my time studying in ...

- Building website with React
- Building smart contract with solidity
- Any latest DeFi protocol in the market

### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

### Bachelor in Mechanical Engineering

# **National Taiwan University**

- Took some financial courses at the same time, including Accounting, Financial Management, Investment, Options, etc.
- I was the captain of the kick-boxing school team in 2019~2020.